OJIMBA CHINEDU GEORGE

Georgeojimba@gmail.com | Linkedin.com/in/georgeojimba 08105295441, 08165524749

Lagos, Nigeria.

PROFILE

I am a personable and knowledgeable technical support engineer with over 3 years of works experience assisting customers both enterprise and end-users with software-related issues in Power Platform, Office 365, and Microsoft Dynamics 365.

I provide in-depth analysis and advisory support regarding issues related to Power Apps, Power Automate, and developing an Environment strategy in Power Platform.

I have outstanding communication skills both verbal and written and as a trained Premier Support engineer, I have been able to nurture new engineers by bringing them up to speed with the best practices and skills needed to thrive and create an amazing customer experience.

I am also a Front-end developer who loves to bring an aesthetic design to life that does not only look or feels good but is also functional and easy to use.

Work Experience

Tek Experts Nigeria - Technical Support Engineer (Power Platform) Sept 2019 – Jan. 2021

Premier Support Engineer / Technical Trainer March. 2021 – Present

Core Task includes:

- Delivering high-quality support services to Microsoft Power platform Enterprise customers by identifying the problem and narrowing it down to a specific component while managing the customer's expectations for resolution.
- I engage both technical and non-technical professionals via phone communications, remote sessions, or via emails to troubleshoot, resolve issues, and document this for both internal and customer reference.
- I analyze and identify bugs with products using telemetry/diagnostic tools and communicate these issues to the Product team while sharing possible alternative solutions pending when this fix is deployed to the customer tenant.
- Nesting and nurturing new engineers by teaching them best practices, monitoring their calls, and supporting them until their go-live time.

Core Task includes:

- Provision of modeling and Analytical support during project discussion with various stakeholders and the team.
- I managed and maintained financial models and documentation relevant to the project.
- Monitor progress made to fulfill all project cost-sharing commitments.

Core Competence / SKills

- I have a "customer first" attitude as well as excellent phone etiquettes and written communication skills.
- I have the necessary soft skills (active listening, empathy) and a unique ability to improvise, grasp new skills and technologies as they unfold.
- Great knowledge of PowerApps, Power Automate, SharePoint Online, SQL fundamentals, REST API, Office 365 integration with Power platform deployment, maintenance, and support of this integrations; as well as excellent troubleshooting/analytical skills.
- Excellent knowledge and flexibility with the use of Microsoft Office suite.

Education

Federal University of Technology Owerri, Imo State (FUTO)

2009 - 2014

Bachelor of Engineering - Electrical Electronics Engineering

Certifications

Microsoft Power Platform Fundamental - PL - 900